This is an extraordinary day for so many reasons, it is special because today we host the class
of 2023.
When I first came on campus, I haven't been here since I left back in 1976 and when you
drive in it says, future home of something fearless.
I love the sound of that guys, the future home of something fearless, that's us.
What cannot be self-taught or learned in isolation is the ability to be changed, molded and inspired
by the world around us.
Be memorable, but be memorable for all the right reasons.
We are tip and strong.
Congratulations class of 2023, give yourself a round of applause.
You did it.
Congratulations to the classes of 2022 and 2023.
Good luck and good tips.